Ann Byykkonen

FRONT END DEVELOPER

https://abyykkonen.github.io/annbyykkonen.github.io/

ABOUT

I'm a self-driven, value-oriented person. I am a positive force that brings focused energy to every office I enter and every project I touch. I have over a decade of experience in customer focused positions. I can communicate across differences, lead and support with confidence, and skillfully navigate with others has allowed me to become the engaged, motivating employee you always want on your team.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer, Autodidact Udemy Student

November 2020 - February 2021

- Solo Project: The Waverly Inn
 - I sought to create a website that was easy for the customers to use.
 - This project was created with HTML and CSS
- Solo Project: Opal's Design
 - My goal for this project was to create a central focused project that allowed the customer to see different focal points throughout the website.
 - This project was created with HTML and CSS

Throughout my process I have learned both the front end and the back end. This process has shown me how to create a website that is appealing to the customers.

White Birch Dental, Princeton, MN— Office Manager

February 2019 - Present

- Prepare the monthly financial statements, budget variance reports, fixed asset entries and account payable
- Formulate year end financial statements and taxes
- Educate and train new and existing employees
- Process payroll and employee benefits
- Develop and implement policies and strategies for the clinic
- Gather and develop marketing strategy for the clinic

Fairview Homecare and Hospice, Princeton, MN— Patient Service Coordinator

January 2017 - February 2019

- Schedule and coordinate appoints for clinicians
- Handle complaints and creatively problem solves in the best interest of both customers and the company
- Work collaboratively with the clinicians

Metro Dentalcare, Maple Grove, MN— Practice Manager

August 2011 - January 2017

Prepare the monthly financial statements, budget variance

7821 115th Ave
PRINCETON, MN 55371
(320) 266-5512
a.bvvkkonen@gmail.com

SKILLS

Leadership

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

SQL

Budgets and financial reporting

Reconcile financial statements

Human Resources

Microsoft Office

Quickbooks

Customer Service

Business Systems

Project Management

EDUCATION

Udemy BootcampFull Stack Developer
2020-2021

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration Northwestern College 2009-2011

Associates Degree in Accounting University of Phoenix, Axia 2007-2009 reports, fixed asset entries and account payable for five dental offices

- Educate and train new and existing employees
- Process payroll and employee benefits for 25 employees
- Develop and implement policies and strategies for the clinic
- Work with employees to increase individual performance and set improvement goals

PROJECTS

Expansion of clinic- *Added more rooms to clinic*Developed the renovation strategy and oversaw the \$150,000 clinic remodel while open for business.

Opening a new clinic - *Opened two dental clinics*Oversaw each one of the \$1 million dollar projects. Helped to keep the projects running smoothly and on schedule for the opening day so we would be open for business on schedule.